Department of Physical Education and Athletics Records UA046
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, negatives, and Scientific Baseball (manual), 1870 -- 2013; 1950 -- 1990; UA046.003; 29.8 Linear Feet; 490 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts football game, 1972; UA046.003.DO.04537; Cushner, Stuart (Box data_value_missing_550aac38ea5460c2b53fb0908e25e7ba)
  - Tufts football game, 1972; UA046.003.DO.04538; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_550aac38ea5460c2b53fb0908e25e7ba)
  - Tufts soccer team, 1946 -- 1947; UA046.003.DO.04539; Dwight Davis Photo (Box data_value_missing_550aac38ea5460c2b53fb0908e25e7ba)
    Athletics; Soccer; photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts varsity football team, fall, 1972; UA046.003.DO.04540; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_550aac38ea5460c2b53fb0908e25e7ba)
  - Tufts football team, 1953; UA046.003.DO.04541; Dwight Davis Photo (Box data_value_missing_550aac38ea5460c2b53fb0908e25e7ba)
  - Tufts men's swim team, 1970 -- 1971; UA046.003.DO.04542; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_550aac38ea5460c2b53fb0908e25e7ba)
    Athletics; Swimming; photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts cheerleading team, 1974; UA046.003.DO.04543; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Athletics; Women; Cheerleading; photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts cheerleaders, 1971; UA046.003.DO.04544; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_550aac38ea5460c2b53fb0908e25e7ba)
    Women; Athletics; Cheerleading; photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts football team, 1978; UA046.003.DO.04545; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_550aac38ea5460c2b53fb0908e25e7ba)
  - Tufts football team, fall, 1981; UA046.003.DO.04546; Young, Donald T. (Box data_value_missing_550aac38ea5460c2b53fb0908e25e7ba)
  - Tufts football team, 1973; UA046.003.DO.04548; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_550aac38ea5460c2b53fb0908e25e7ba)
  - Women's basketball team, 1971 -- 1972; UA046.003.DO.04549; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
    Women; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts varsity men's basketball team, 1971 -- 1972; UA046.003.DO.04550; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
  - Tufts women's basketball team, 1980; UA046.003.DO.04551; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
    Students; Women; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts women's basketball team, 1985; UA046.003.DO.04552; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
    Women; Students; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts men's basketball team, 1980 -- 1981; UA046.003.DO.04553; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
  - Tufts lacrosse team, 1972 -- 1973; UA046.003.DO.04554; Young, Donald T. (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
    Students; Athletics; Lacrosse; photographic print; Black students
  - Men's track meet, 1957; UA046.003.DO.04555; Percival (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
    Students; People; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print
  - Tufts track team, 1953; UA046.003.DO.04556; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts track meet, 1955; UA046.003.DO.04557; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
  - Tufts lacrosse team, 1971; UA046.003.DO.04558; Young, Donald T. (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
  - Tufts junior varsity women's lacrosse team, 1976; UA046.003.DO.04559; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
    Women; Students; Athletics; Lacrosse; photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts women's lacrosse team, 1985; UA046.003.DO.04560; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
  - Tufts men's varsity lacrosse team, spring, 1972; UA046.003.DO.04561; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
  - Tufts men's lacrosse team, 1980; UA046.003.DO.04562; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
  - Tufts track meet, 1950; UA046.003.DO.04563; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students; Tufts University
  - Tufts track team, 1959; UA046.003.DO.04564; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Tufts track runner Basil Ince, 1959; UA046.003.DO.04565; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students; Ince, Basil
  - Tufts track meet, 1955; UA046.003.DO.04566; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Tufts track meet, 1955; UA046.003.DO.04567; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    People; Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print
  - Tufts track meet, 1955; UA046.003.DO.04568; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Tufts women's track team, 1984; UA046.003.DO.04569; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
    Students; Athletics; Track (Women's); photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts men's cross country team, 1970; UA046.003.DO.04570; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
    Students; Athletics; Cross Country; photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts men's basketball team, 1978 -- 1979; UA046.003.DO.04571; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
  - Tufts men's basketball team, 1978 -- 1979; UA046.003.DO.04572; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_a8603c4674095a2147d6aa1648b83b27)
  - Tufts men's basketball team, 1976 -- 1977; UA046.003.DO.04573; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
  - Tufts men's varsity track team, 1972; UA046.003.DO.04574; Young, Donald T. (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
  - Tufts College indoor track team, 1965; UA046.003.DO.04575; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
  - Tufts women's indoor track team, 1979 -- 1980; UA046.003.DO.04576; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
    Students; Athletics; photographic print; Track (Women's); Black students
  - Tufts men's indoor track team, 1979 -- 1980; UA046.003.DO.04577; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
  - Tufts women's indoor track team, 1977 -- 1978; UA046.003.DO.04578; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
    Women; Students; Athletics; Track and Field; photographic print; Black students
  - Jackson College varsity basketball team, 1974; UA046.003.DO.04579; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
  - Tufts men's basketball team, 1973 -- 1974; UA046.003.DO.04580; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
  - Tufts women's volleyball team, 1981; UA046.003.DO.04581; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
    Women; Athletics; Volleyball; photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts men's outdoor track team, 1971; UA046.003.DO.04582; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
    Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students
  - Tufts outdoor track team, 1970; UA046.003.DO.04583; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
  - Tufts indoor track team, 1970 -- 1971; UA046.003.DO.04584; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
    Note: the item number and the DO number DO NOT match because of a data entry error.
  - Rocky Carzo and Brooks Johnson, 1983; UA046.003.DO.04585; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
    Athletics; photographic print; Black students; Carzo, Rocco "Rocky"; Johnson, Brooks T.
  - Troy Cooper, A'83, 1982 -- 1983; UA046.003.DO.04586; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
  - Tufts football team co-captains, 1978; UA046.003.DO.04587; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
    Season Captains Bob Lederman and Terry Richards with head coach Vic Gatto.
  - Rocky Carzo, Branwen Smith-King, Vera Stenhouse, and her mother, 1991; UA046.003.DO.04588; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Students; Women; Athletics; photographic print; Black students; Carzo, Rocco "Rocky"; Stenhouse, Vera; Smith-King, Branwen
  - Tufts track team, 1956; UA046.003.DO.04589; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
  - Basil Ince at track meet, 1959; UA046.003.DO.04590; Unknown (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
    Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students; Ince, Basil
  - Tufts indoor track team, 1950 -- 1951; UA046.003.DO.04591; Dwight Davis Photo (Box data_value_missing_cab8542f36167c91d1f2716e4b154a30)
  - Rodney Pete Watson, 1970; UA046.003.DO.04593; Unknown (Box Shared 70)
    Students; Athletics; Football; photographic print; Black students; Watson, Rodney Peter
  - Ronnie Woods, 1978; UA046.003.DO.04594; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Students; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Black students; Woods, Ronnie
  - Tim Scaggs, 1979; UA046.003.DO.04595; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Students; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Black students; Scaggs, Tim
  - Jumbo Club, Sam Bryant, second from left, rear, 1971; UA046.003.DO.04596; Unknown (Box Shared 70)
    Athletics; photographic print; Black students; Bryant, Sam; Jumbo Club
  - Dennis Mink, 1974; UA046.003.DO.04597; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Tufts men's basketball team, 1973 -- 1974; UA046.003.DO.04598; Unknown (Box Shared 70)
  - Bob Winn, cheerleaders, and men's basketball team, 1981 -- 1982; UA046.003.DO.04599; Unknown (Box Shared 70)
    Students; Cheerleading; Basketball; Athletics; photographic print; Black students; Winn, Robert
  - Tufts men's basketball team, 1975 -- 1976; UA046.003.DO.04600; Unknown (Box Shared 70)
  - All Sports Award, Robert Jones (A1953) on right, 1952; UA046.003.DO.04601; Dwight Davis Photo (Box Shared 70)
    Students; Athletics; Awards; photographic print; Black students; Jones, Robert
  - Tufts indoor track team, 1954; UA046.003.DO.04602; Dwight Davis Photo (Box Shared 70)
  - Tufts outdoor track team, 1950; UA046.003.DO.04603; Dwight Davis Photo (Box Shared 70)
  - Tufts men's basketball team, 1975; UA046.003.DO.04604; Unknown (Box Shared 70)
  - Brooks Johnson running a race, 1950; UA046.003.DO.04605; Unknown (Box Shared 70)
    Athletics; Students; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students; Johnson, Brooks T.
  - Basil Ince, indoor track team, 1959; UA046.003.DO.04607; Unknown (Box Shared 70)
  - Tufts men's track team, 1952; UA046.003.DO.04608; Duette (Box Shared 70)
  - Robert Jones, track team, 1953; UA046.003.DO.04609; Dwight Davis Photo (Box Shared 70)
    Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students; Jones, Robert
  - Tufts men's lacrosse team in front of Cousens Gymnasium, 1979; UA046.003.DO.04610; Unknown (Box Shared 70)
  - Tufts football team in front of Cousens Gymnasium, 1989; UA046.003.DO.04611; Unknown (Box Shared 70)
  - Dennis Mink, 1974; UA046.003.DO.04613; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
  - Joe Dunston, 1974; UA046.003.DO.04614; Unknown (Box Shared 20)
    Students; Athletics; Basketball; photographic print; Black students; Dunston, Joe
  - Unidentified basketball player, 1973 -- 1974; UA046.003.DO.04615; Unknown (Box Shared 37)
  - Varsity Club, 1952; UA046.003.DO.04616; Dwight Davis Photo (Box Shared 37)
    Students; Athletics; Awards; photographic print; Black students; Varsity Club
  - Tufts men's indoor track team, 1948 -- 1949; UA046.003.DO.04617; Dwight Davis Photo (Box Shared 37)
  - Sam Bryant, Rocky Carzo, Bob Malay and other unidentified men, 1980; UA046.003.DO.04619; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 37)
    Students; Athletics; photographic print; Black students; Bryant, Sam; Malay, Robert; Carzo, Rocco "Rocky"
  - Jeff Bloom, Steve Centrella (#2), and George Bazos (#8), 1986; UA046.003.DO.04623; Unknown (Box Shared 37)
    People; Students; Athletics; Baseball; photographic print; Bloom, Jeff; Centrella, Steven; Bazos, George
  - Jeff Bloom and Tom Walsh (#7), 1986; UA046.003.DO.04625; Unknown (Box Shared 37)
    Students; People; Athletics; Baseball; photographic print; Bloom, Jeff; Walsh, Tom
  - Professor T. J. Anderson (left) and Rocky Carzo (right) at T. J. Celebration, Spring, 1995; UA046.003.DO.05020; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
    Celebrations; People; photographic print; Carzo, Rocco "Rocky"; Anderson, T. J.; Tufts University
  - Rich Gachetti, 1969; UA046.003.DO.05021; Raphael, David (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; Football; People; photographic print; Gachetti, Rich; Tufts University
  - Rich Gachetti (88) and Cohen, 1969; UA046.003.DO.05022; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 21)
  - Mark Buben, 1978; UA046.003.DO.05023; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; Football; People; photographic print; Buben, Mark; Tufts University
  - Lance Johnson, 1968; UA046.003.DO.05024; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 21)
    Athletics; Football; People; photographic print; Johnson, Lance; Tufts University
  - Unidentified football coach and players posing with the statue of Jumbo outside Wessell Library, 1964; UA046.003.DO.05025; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; Football; People; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Co-captains David Wells (33) and Norman Wright (31), 1957; UA046.003.DO.05026; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; Football; People; photographic print; Wells, David; Wright, Norman; Tufts University
  - Co-captains Joe Asiaf (62) and George Kurker (75) outside Goddard Chapel, 1957; UA046.003.DO.05027; Davis, Dwight (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; Football; People; photographic print; Asiaf, J.; Kurker, George; Tufts University
  - Rocky Carzo with coaches Lauletta and Vandersea and unidentified players, 1968; UA046.003.DO.05028; Chrukin, Jeffrey S. (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; Football; People; photographic print; Carzo, Rocco "Rocky"; Tufts University
  - Caitlin Murphy, J2000, UA046.003.DO.05098; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    People; Track and Field; Women; Athletics; photographic print; Murphy, Caitlin
  - Caitlin Murphy, J2000, UA046.003.DO.05099; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
  - Tufts golf star, Barrie Bruce, A1963, UA046.003.DO.05100; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
    People; Students; Athletics; Golf; photographic print; Bruce, Barrie
  - Diane Wilcox, lacrosse player, 1982; UA046.003.DO.05101; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    People; Students; Women; Athletics; Lacrosse; photographic print; Wilcox, Diane
  - Fred Hintlian, 4 times All-American, n.d., UA046.003.DO.05102; Kahn, David M. (Box Shared 21)
    No date available
    People; Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Hintlian, Fred
  - Jeff Taglienti, Tufts baseball player, 1997; UA046.003.DO.05103; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    People; Athletics; Baseball; photographic print; Taglienti, Jeff
  - Bill Canon, 1988; UA046.003.DO.05104; Bushell, S. (Box Shared 21)
    Athletics; Baseball; People; photographic print; Canon, Bill; Tufts University
  - Dan Callahan, 2002; UA046.003.DO.05105; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    Athletics; Baseball; People; photographic print; Callahan, Dan; Tufts University
  - Bob Berluti, 1974; UA046.003.DO.05106; Liu, Karen (Box Shared 21)
    Athletics; Baseball; People; photographic print; Berluti, Bob; Tufts University
  - Todd Ranboli, 1990; UA046.003.DO.05107; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    Athletics; Baseball; People; photographic print; Ranboli, Todd; Tufts University
  - Sara Richardson, 1987; UA046.003.DO.05109; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; Lacrosse; People; photographic print; Richardson, Sarah; Tufts University
  - Kathy Whitcomb, 1975; UA046.003.DO.05110; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; Track (Women's); Cross Country; People; photographic print; Whitcomb, Kathy; Tufts University
  - Women's lacrosse, 1987; UA046.003.DO.05111; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; Lacrosse; People; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Women's lacrosse, 1982; UA046.003.DO.05112; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1988; UA046.003.DO.05113; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
  - Women's lacrosse, 1989; UA046.003.DO.05114; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
  - Rich Giachetti, three year national leader in receptions, 1969; UA046.003.DO.05115; Rush, Jeffrey (Box Shared 21)
    Athletics; Football; People; photographic print; Giachetti, Rich; Tufts University
  - Rob Bass, 1969; UA046.003.DO.05116; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 21)
    Athletics; Football; People; photographic print; Bass, Rob; Tufts University
  - Brooks Johnson and Dr. Jean Mayer, 1985; UA046.003.DO.05117; Costerus (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; People; photographic print; Mayer, Jean; Johnson, Brooks T.; Tufts University
  - Women's indoor track team, 1979 -- 1980; UA046.003.DO.05118; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; Track (Women's); People; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Coach Gatto with captains of football team, 1979; UA046.003.DO.05119; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
  - Fred Hintlian, All American and NCAA Division III Champion, 1976; UA046.003.DO.05120; Unknown (Box Shared 71)
    Athletics; Track (Men's); People; photographic print; Hintlian, Fred; Tufts University
  - Women's basketball game, 1961; UA046.003.DO.05147; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    People; Women; Basketball; Athletics; photographic print
  - Women's field hockey team, left rear: Maryann Conigliaro, J1968, fifth from left: Roberta Chenko, J1968, third from left in front: Vicki Gillis Russell, J1968, 1965; UA046.003.DO.05148; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    People; Women; Field Hockey; Athletics; photographic print; Conigliaro, Maryann; Chenko, Roberta; Russell, Vicki Gillis
  - Football team, 1979; UA046.003.DO.05157; Unknown (Box Shared 72)
    People; Students; Athletics; Football; copy negative --image/tiff
  - Men's soccer team in front of Ballou Hall, 1972; UA046.003.DO.05158; Young, Donald T. (Box Shared 72)
  - Two Tufts field hockey players and coach, 1981; UA046.003.DO.05186; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    Marisa Dido, center
    Athletics; Field Hockey; People; Students; photographic print; Dido, Marisa; Tufts University
  - Two Tufts field hockey players, 1981; UA046.003.DO.05187; Unknown (Box Shared 21)
    Athletics; Field Hockey; People; Students; photographic print; Tufts University
  - Tufts Field Hockey Team, 1981; UA046.003.DO.05188; Unknown (Box Shared 72)
    Record: 11-1-1; MAIAW Tourney Champions front row,(left to right) Lu Ronco, Jean Mockard, Michelle Carlson, Alison Moore, Mary Dickson, Donna Wells, Jodi Paglia, Barb Richter. Second row, (left to right)Head Coach Marisa Dido, Linda Russell, Donna Kennedy, Jean Sanfacon, Co-Capt. Nica Cudahy, Co-Capt. Barb Sprague, Co-Capt. Diane Wilcox, Arlene Jordan, Eve Elliot, Kate Donovan, Asst. Coach Mary Kay Finnerty, Asst. Coach Cherly Murtaugh.
  - Long jump photograph of Bruce Moore, circa 1956; UA046.005878 (Box Shared 145, Folder 7)
    Photograph taken in the Dusault Cage by a school photographer. The image is a composite of three separate jumps.
- Videos, 1930 -- 2006; UA046.004; 0.2 Linear Feet; 4 Audiovisual Object(s); 2 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains game footage of the Tufts football, baseball, men's and women's lacrosse, and swimming teams, circa 1930-2000.
  This series is not arranged.
  - Football game footage, 1930 -- 1940; UA046.004.196.00001; Manly, Lewis F. (Box 196)
    Footage of an unknown Tufts football game.
    tape reels
  - Football game footage, 1930 -- 1940; UA046.004.196.00002; Manly, Lewis F. (Box 196)
  - Baseball game footage: Tufts v. Northeastern, 1966; UA046.004.196.00003 (Box 196)
  - Baseball game footage: Tufts v. Boston College, 1966; UA046.004.196.00004 (Box 196)
  - Tufts University 1992 New England Swimming Championships at Bowdoin College, UA046.004.197.00001 (Box 197)
    Running time: 4 hrs 45 mins
    videocassettes
  - Women's lacrosse game footage: Tufts v. Trinity College, 2000; UA046.004.198.00001 (Box 198)
    Original label reads "Tufts 8 Trin 4 Lax 00".
  - Men's lacrosse, mid-season highlights, 2006; UA046.004.199.00001 (Case 199)
    Original label reads "Tufts Mid-Season Highlights 2006"
    DVD
  - Men's lacrosse game footage: Tufts v. Middlebury College, NESCAC, 2006; UA046.004.200.00001 (Case 200)
    Original label reads "Tufts v. Midd NESCACS '06"
- Scrapbooks, 1916 -- 1981; 1950 -- 1970; UA046.005; 15.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains scrapbooks 1937 to 1981, which were created by the Athletic Department to document sporting events throughout the year.
  This series is arranged chronologically, except box #40.
  - Scrapbook football and basketball, UA046.005.040.00001 (Box UA046 Shared 2)
  - Scrapbook basketball, 1949; UA046.005.040.00002 (Box UA046 Shared 2)
  - Scrapbook football, 1947; UA046.005.040.00003 (Box UA046 Shared 2)
  - Scrapbook football, 1947, UA046.005.040.00004 (Box UA046 Shared 2)
  - Scrapbook football, 1948, UA046.005.040.00005 (Box UA046 Shared 2)
  - Scrapbook football, 1949, UA046.005.040.00006 (Box UA046 Shared 2)
  - Scrapbook football, 1952 -- 1953; UA046.005.040.00007 (Box UA046 Shared 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1937 -- 1968; UA046.005.073.001 (Box 73)
  - Scrapbook, 1945 -- 1946; UA046.005.074.001 (Box 74)
  - Scrapbook, 1946 -- 1947; UA046.005.075.001 (Box 75)
  - Scrapbook, 1963 -- 1964; UA046.005.076.001 (Box 76)
  - Scrapbook, 1964, UA046.005.077.001 (Box 77)
  - Scrapbook, 1965, UA046.005.078.001 (Box 78)
  - Scrapbook, 1965 -- 1966; UA046.005.079.001 (Box 79)
  - Scrapbook, 1966, UA046.005.080.001 (Box 80)
  - Scrapbook, 1966 -- 1967; UA046.005.081.001 (Box 81)
  - Scrapbook, 1967, 1966; UA046.005.082.001 (Box 82)
  - Scrapbook, 1967 -- 1968; UA046.005.083.001 (Box 83)
  - Scrapbook, 1967 -- 1981; UA046.005.084.001 (Box 84)
  - Scrapbook, 1968, UA046.005.085.001 (Box 85)
  - Scrapbook, 1968 -- 1969; UA046.005.086.001 (Box 86)
  - Scrapbook, 1969, UA046.005.087.001 (Box 87)
  - Scrapbook, 1969 -- 1970; UA046.005.088.001 (Box 88)
  - Scrapbook, 1970, UA046.005.089.001 (Box 89)
  - Scrapbook, 1970 -- 1971; UA046.005.090.001 (Box 90)
  - Scrapbook, 1971, UA046.005.091.001 (Box 91)
  - Scrapbook, 1971 -- 1972; UA046.005.092.001 (Box 92)
  - Scrapbook, 1972, UA046.005.093.001 (Box 93)
  - Scrapbook, 1974 -- 1975; UA046.005.094.001 (Box 94)
  - Scrapbook, 1974 -- 1975; UA046.005.095.001 (Box 95)
  - Scrapbook, 1975 -- 1976; UA046.005.096.001 (Box 96)
  - Scrapbook, 1976 -- 1977; UA046.005.097.001 (Box 97)
  - Scrapbook, 1964 -- 1965; UA046.005.098.00001 (Box 98)
  - Scrapbook, Irvin Wilkinson, 1926 -- 1930; UA046.005.099.00001 (Volume 99)
    scrapbooks
  - Scrapbook, George White [1 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00001 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
    Newspaper Clippings, Photos
  - Scrapbook, George White [2 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00002 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [3 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00003 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [4 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00004 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [5 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00005 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [6 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00006 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [7 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00007 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [8 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00008 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [9 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00009 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [10 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00010 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [11 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00011 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [12 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00012 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [13 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00013 (Box UA046 Shared 1)
  - Scrapbook, George White [14 of 19], 1916 -- 1923; UA046.005.161.00014 (Box UA046 Shared 1)